let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: 'My father is often at work.',
    answer: "Souvent",
    options: [
      "Souvent",
      "Toujours",
      "Jamais",
      "Parfois",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: 'I am always late.',
    answer: "Toujours",
    options: [
      "Parfois",
      "Souvent",
      "Toujours",
      "Jamais",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: 'She rarely goes to the beach.',
    answer: "Rarement",
    options: [
      "Souvent",
      "Toujours",
      "Rarement",
      "Parfois",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: 'We do sports regularly.',
    answer: "Régulièrement",
    options: [
      "Toujours",
      "Régulièrement",
      "Parfois",
      "Jamais",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: 'You sometimes go out in the evening.',
    answer: "Parfois",
    options: [
      "Parfois",
      "Souvent",
      "Jamais",
      "Toujours",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: 'They never eat fast food.',
    answer: "Jamais",
    options: [
      "Souvent",
      "Rarement",
      "Toujours",
      "Jamais",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: 'We are always together.',
    answer: "Toujours",
    options: [
      "Parfois",
      "Toujours",
      "Souvent",
      "Jamais",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: 'It often rains in the fall.',
    answer: "Souvent",
    options: [
      "Souvent",
      "Rarement",
      "Toujours",
      "Jamais",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: 'She always studies before exams.',
    answer: "Toujours",
    options: [
      "Jamais",
      "Parfois",
      "Souvent",
      "Toujours",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: 'They rarely travel to France.',
    answer: "Rarement",
    options: [
      "Jamais",
      "Parfois",
      "Rarement",
      "Souvent",
    ]
  }
];
